<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="OpenDentalDiffDocumentation.xsl"?>
<database version="18.2.11.0">
    <table name="clearinghouse">
        <summary></summary>
        <column order="29" name="IsAttachmentSendAllowed" type="tinyint(4)">
            <summary>Currently only used for DentalXChange's attachment service. This indicates that the user has set up the attachment service and would like to use it in Open Dental.</summary>
        </column>
    </table>
    <table name="emailmessage">
        <summary></summary>
        <column order="17" name="IsHtml" type="tinyint(4)">
            <summary>True if the email message was sent in HTML.  False if Plain Text.</summary>
        </column>
    </table>
    <table name="insplan">
        <summary></summary>
        <column order="39" name="HasPpoSubstWriteoffs" type="tinyint(4)">
            <summary>True by default.  When a plan allows downgrading procedures and this field is false, the writeoff will be $0 and the difference
            between the proc fee and the insurance estimate will be the patient portion.</summary>
        </column>
    </table>
    <table name="provider">
        <summary></summary>
        <column order="44" name="DateTerm" type="date">
            <summary>The date that the provider's term ends. This can be used to prevent appointments from being scheduled, appointments from being 
            marked complete, prescriptions from being prescribed, and claims from being sent.</summary>
        </column>
    </table>
    <table name="sheet">
        <summary></summary>
        <column order="18" name="DateTSheetEdited" type="datetime">
            <summary>The date and time the sheet was inserted or last time someone opened the sheet and clicked OK on FormSheetFillEdit.
            Gets updated even if no changes were made to the sheet or sheetfields, because we don't want to do the lengthy work of comparing all fields.
            Used when editing a sheet to warn user if the sheet has been edited by someone else.</summary>
        </column>
    </table>
    <table name="smstomobile">
        <summary></summary>
        <column order="17" name="MsgDiscountUSD" type="float">
            <summary>Any discount applied to this message. 
            If a particular messages has a MsgDiscountUSD &gt; 0  then the MsgChargeUSD will reflect the charge to the customer after the discount has already been applied. 
            Multi-part messages will still be charged the wholesale rate for all parts after the first part.
            To calculate the typical charge that this customer would pay without the discount use MsgChargeUSD + MsgDiscountUSD.
            To calculate the percentage discounted off standard charges use (MsgDiscountUSD / (MsgChargeUSD + MsgDiscountUSD)).</summary>
        </column>
    </table>
    <table name="supplyorder">
        <summary></summary>
        <column order="5" name="UserNum" type="bigint(20)" fk="userod">
            <summary>FK to userod.UserNum. User that placed the order, is editable.</summary>
        </column>
        <column order="6" name="ShippingCharge" type="double">
            <summary>The order's shipping charge.</summary>
        </column>
    </table>
    <table name="timecardrule">
        <summary></summary>
        <column order="6" name="MinClockInTime" type="time">
            <summary>When set this is the earliest an employee can clock in. Otherwise minimum dateTime represents not set.</summary>
        </column>
    </table>
    <table name="wikipage">
        <summary></summary>
        <column order="9" name="PageContentPlainText" type="mediumtext">
            <summary>Content of page stored without any HTML markup or wiki page links.  This plain text allows for easier searching.</summary>
        </column>
    </table>
</database>